UNITE HERE Local 23-25 Files 6200/005
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UNITE HERE Local 23-25 Files
1997-2008
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UNITE HERE
UNITE HERE Local 23-25
6200/005
0.5 cubic feet
0.5 linear ft.
Records.
8255160
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 14, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 25, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6200: UNITE HERE Records
Hotel Employees & Restaurant Employees International Union; UNITE HERE (Organization)
8255160
- Agreement Perfect Manufacturing Co., 2005 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  July 1, 2005
- Edgar Romney Papers, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Cookie's (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Maybar, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Social Security Video Information (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Envelope - Alliance for Retired Americans
- Textbook Scholarship Selection & Award, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Scholarship Selection, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Textbook Scholarship Award Ceremony, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Sourcing, 2005-2008 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Hotel Workers (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Taxpayer Relief Act, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  Chinese & English
- HNY Policy Paper, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- GIDC Board Meeting, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  Thursday, October 27, 2005
- GIDC Board of Directors Meeting, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  October 12, 2006
- Garment Industry Development Corp. Board Meeting, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  December 21, 2007
- Garment Industry Development Corporation Board of Directors Meeting, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  June 28, 2007
- Garment Industry Development Corporation, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- New York State Senate No. 823 Legislative Resolution, 2005-2008 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Solidarity Charter, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- New York State Senate No. 4619 Legislative Resolution, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Save the Garment Center envelope 1, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Save the Garment Center envelope 2, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Save the Garment Center envelope 3, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 23)